我叫巴里·艾伦
My name is Barry Allen,
是现今世上速度最快的人
and I am the fastest man alive.
在外人看来
To the outside world,
我只是个普通的鉴证专员
I'm an ordinary forensic scientist,
但在尖端科研实验室的朋友们的帮助下
but secretly, with the help of my friends at S.T.A.R Labs,
我秘密打击犯罪  寻找跟我一样的超能力者
I fight crime and find other meta-humans like me.
我让杀害母亲的凶手自食其果
I hunted down the man who killed my mother,
但我们的世界
but in doing so,
也因此出现了新的威胁
I opened up our world to new threats.
我是唯一来得及阻止他们的人
And I am the only one fast enough to stop them.
我叫闪电侠
I am The Flash.
《闪电侠》《绿箭》前情回顾
Previously on "The Flash" And "Arrow"...
昨晚闯进大楼的人
The person who broke into my facility last night
是哈里森·威尔斯
was Harrison Wells.
凯特琳·斯诺博士  西斯科·拉蒙
Dr. Caitlin Snow, Cisco Ramon,
来见见地球二来的哈里森·威尔斯博士
meet Dr. Harrison Wells from Earth-2.
我是来帮你的  巴里
I came here to help you, Barry.
他也许不是你们地球上的哈里森·威尔斯
He may not be Harrison Wells from your earth.
但他就和你认识的那个一样有很多秘密
He has just as many secrets as the one you knew.
我有时候会有些感觉  这些震波
I get these feelings sometimes, these vibes.
我不知道怎么触发的  有时它就那么发生了
I'm not sure what triggers it. Sometimes it just happens.
你随时都可以找我倾谈
You can always talk to me.
-搭档  -搭档
- Partners? - Partners.
这是一百万
This is a million dollars.
告诉奥利弗孩子没了  钱就是你的
That money is yours once you tell Oliver that you've lost the baby.
最近我一直在跑
I've been running a lot lately,
试图跑的比以前更快
trying to go faster than I've ever gone before.
因为现在有个人
Because there's someone out there
比我更厉害  更快  也更强
who's better, faster, and stronger than I am,
我要做好准备
and I need to be ready.
但不管我怎样努力  怎样逼着自己进步
But no matter how much I try or how hard I push myself,
我总是面临同样的问题
I keep running into the same problem.
他时速1375公里了
He just hit 1,375.
他跑最快时候时速是多少
What's the fastest Barry's run?
2250公里出头吧  他穿越时间的那次
Little over Mach two, when he ran back in time.
这可不妙
That's not good.
很好  巴里
That's good, Barry.
我们的任务很艰巨
We have our work cut out for us.
我的速度没提上去  是不是
I'm not getting faster, am I?
确实没有
No, you're not.
好吧  我们来解决下这个问题
All right, well, let's fix this, right?
我这个速度没法打败极速
I mean, I can't beat Zoom at this speed.
我站在他身边就像是静止不动一样
It felt like I was standing still next to him.
因为确实如此
That's because you practically were.
极速的速度至少是你现在的三四倍
Zoom is at least three, four times faster than you at this point.
他为什么会比巴里和杰伊快这么多
How is he so much faster than Barry is and Jay was?
生理  体型  力量  有很多因素
Physiology, form, strength, could be a number of things--
态度  饮食
attitude, diet.
好吧  一定有什么办法的
Okay, all right, well, there's got to be something we can do about it,
我们一起想想吧
so let's just figure it out...
快点想  好吗
Fast, okay?
我得走了  我要去见帕蒂
All right, I got to go. I'm meeting Patty.
回见  谢谢你们
I'll see you. Thank you.
我们要怎么帮巴里
So how are we going to help Barry?
我没主意了
I'm out of ideas,
你的建议我们也全部尝试过了
and we've tried everything you've suggested.
并不是全部
Well, not everything.
欢迎回来
Welcome home.
-有什么麻烦吗  -没有
- Any trouble? - Nah.
但信不信由你  船上有个偷渡者
But believe it or not, we got ourselves a stowaway.
-他说自己名字了吗  -没说
- He give you his name? - Didn't say.
在禁闭室安静地坐了三个礼拜
Sat in the brig silent for three weeks.
我们发现他的时候  他穿着这个
He was all decked out in this when we found him.
-天哪  这有多少把  -32
- Jeez, how many are there? - 32.
过不了多久  我就会用鲜血打磨它们
And I'll polish them all in blood before long.
这场狩猎我期待已久
I've waited a long time for this hunt,
而你们将我带到了猎物跟前
and you have brought me very close to my prey.
先生  你戴着手铐可没法狩猎
Mister, you're not going to do any hunting in those handcuffs.
但船长  是你戴着手铐
Oh, but, Captain, you're wearing the cuffs.
谁教你的  胡迪尼吗
Who taught you that-- Houdini?
“哈里·胡迪尼 20世纪初著名魔术大师”
事实上  是我教的他
Actually, I taught him.
另一份祭品很快就会奉上
Soon another sacrifice will be made.
我能感觉到你的存在
I feel you out there.
天哪  简直就是个大屠杀
Man, this was a bloodbath.
凶手只有一个人
Done by one person.
一个人杀了这么多人
One person did all this?
是啊  从血态能看出来
Oh, yeah, you can see from the blood pattern.
先是射杀这个人  然后是警官
This guy was shot first, then the police chief,
然后捅这三个人  最后给船长补了一刀
then these three were stabbed before finishing off the captain.
你觉得是超能力者做的吗
Do you think a meta-human did it?
说不好  但我发现
I don't know, but I found this
遇刺者的伤口都有这个
in all of the stab victims' wounds.
某种隐晶质  最有可能是燧石
It's some type of cryptocrystalline-- flint, most likely--
大概是打斗时从刀刃被剥落下来的
probably broke off the blade during the fight.
我去做个测试鉴定一下
I'll run it to make sure.
咱们去查查有哪些商店卖这种燧石刀
Let's see what stores sell those kind of flint knives.
没问题
Will do.
我回头给你打电话
And, uh, I'll call you later.
-好的  -好的
- Okay. - Okay.
真可爱
So cute.
你们在试图避免在我面前秀恩爱
You guys are trying not to be affectionate in front of me.
没有啊  我们只是拿出了专业精神
Oh, no, we're just showing some professionalism.
没错
Yeah.
成为授权管理人的好处
Advantages of a trusting manager.
这里可发生过好多事
Oh, a lot's gone down in this place.
很好
Nice.
怎么了
So what's up?
我以为我们要一起吃晚饭
I thought we were gonna go to dinner.
天呐
Whoa.
这是怎么回事
What's going on here?
我拿不定主意到底要去哪家餐厅
I couldn't decide which restaurant to go to,
所以我想着我们可以自己做
so I thought we would create our own.
来看看
Voila.
排骨  薯泥还有芦笋
Short rib, Yukon gold puree, and asparagus.
要吃蔬菜营养才均衡
Got to have a vegetable.
这主意很好
This is nice.
我喜欢做饭
I like to cook.
我不知道你喜欢红酒还是白酒  所以
I didn't know if you like red or white, so...
我两种都拿了
I got you both.
两瓶酒啊
Ooh, two bottles.
你不觉得这样有点危险吗
That's kind dangerous, don't you think?
你不会突然就推门走出去吧
You're not gonna run away all of a sudden, are you?
相信我  我会一直陪着你的
Trust me, I'm staying by your side as long as possible.
那就好
Good.
我觉得过去几周和你在一起
You know, it's been really great
我过得很开心
hanging out these last few weeks.
这让我感觉好了很多
And it's helped make the move a lot easier, so...
谢谢你
thanks.
不用客气
You're very welcome.
[古语]
不好意思  你是怎么进来的
Sorry. How did you get in here?
先生  这家店已经打烊了
Hey, man, this place is closed.
你今生和那些前世里一样美丽
You are just as beautiful in this life as any other,
女祭司茶雅拉
Priestess Chay-Ara.
女祭司
Priestess?
你现在最好离开这里  老兄
You're going to have to go, dude.
那也得带上她
Oh, not without her...
老兄
dude.
我的天  西斯科
Oh, my God. Cisco.
我不明白  你想要什么
I don't understand. What do you want?
我以为我已经说得很清楚了
I believe I was clear.
求救信号
发送中
西斯科·拉蒙
警报
地点  吉特咖啡店
肯德拉不会跟你走的  高地人
Kendra's not going anywhere with you, Highlander.
你现在改名叫这个了啊
Oh, is that your name now?
肯德拉  真无聊
Kendra-- quite boring.
不过这名字很明显让你融入了这里
I believe it allowed you to blend in for a while.
把她交给我  我可以让你死得痛快点
Now, give her to me, and I'll make your death fast.
你想都别想
It ain't gonna happen.
这里没你的事了
You are done here, pal.
他也是
So is he!
谢天谢地  巴里
Thank God, Barry.
伙计  别这样
Dude, come on.
真不敢相信你居然是闪电侠
I can't believe you're The Flash.
而你是闪电侠的搭档
And that you work with The Flash.
是啊  这件事还是别说出去
Yeah, let's keep that on the DL.
这把匕首跟杀死码头那帮人的凶器一样
This is the same knife that was used to kill the men at the docks.
现场残留物与它吻合
Residue is a perfect match.
-所以凶手是同一人  -没错
- So it is the same guy. - Definitely.
可是这些匕首年代久远
But the thing is, these blades are old,
好几个世纪那么远
centuries old.
你知道那个人为什么要找你吗
Do you have any idea why this guy would be after you?
不知道  我以前从没见过他
No, I've never seen him before in my life.
但是他肯定认识你
Well, he was certainly acting like he knew you.
他一直叫她女祭司茶雅拉
He kept calling her Priestess Chay-Ara.
那是科普特语
That's Coptic.
-你是说古埃及语吗  -没错
- You mean Egyptian? - That's right.
我自幼在威斯康辛州长大
Well, I grew up in Wisconsin,
我也从没离开过美国  所以
and I've never even left the States, so...
很明显  这个人很危险
This guy, he's clearly incredibly dangerous,
所以你怎么样也得让我们保护你
so I need you to at least let us try to protect you.
我能派警察保护她
I can put a detail on her.
你没看见那个人  乔
You didn't see this guy, Joe.
无意冒犯  但我觉得警察保护不了她
No offense, but I don't think a cop is going to be able to protect her.
是不能  但我们可以找朋友帮忙
No, but we do have a few friends who could lend a hand.
不过我们得离开中城
But we're going to need to leave Central City.
去哪里
And go where?
你确定要去星城吗
You really want to go to Star City?
我不需要绿箭那伙人的帮助
Come on, we don't need Team Arrow's help.
我觉得我们需要
Yeah, I think we do, man.
你以前收拾过的超能力者里面
Man, you've fought meta-humans
比这个扔飞镖厉害的也大有人在
with abilities a lot worse than knife-throwing.
我觉得他不是超能力者
I don't think this guy's a meta-human.
他身上有一种不同的感觉
There's something different about him,
有种神秘的气息
something, ah, mystical.
神秘的气息
Mystical, really?
我们能阻止超能力者  是因为我们懂科学
We stop meta-humans because we're scientists.
我们能找出他们的弱点
We can figure out what their weaknesses are,
但是我们对付这一类人没有经验
but we don't have any experience when it comes to guys like this,
这种用魔法的  他们有经验
with magic. They do.
所以这事跟极速没关系  是吗
This wouldn't have anything to do with Zoom, would it?
没关系
No.
我只想保护好肯德拉
I'm just trying to keep Kendra safe.
这是最好的办法
This is the best way to do that.
好吧  我跟你一起去
Right. Okay, I'm with you.
可是我们怎么知道奥利弗和他的朋友
But how do we even know Oliver and them
有这个时间协助我们
even have time to help us?
他们还能有多忙啊
How busy can they be?
天眼会
星城分会
这真好玩
Oh, gosh, that's fun.
我可以这样玩一天
I really could do this all day.
把门打开
Open it up.
他们最起码要试着藏一下这化学炸弹吧
They could've at least tried to hide this chemical bomb.
真是活该  现在被偷走还反过来对付他们
Serves them right, it getting stolen and used against them.
你带着弓箭来枪战了吗
Oh, you brought arrows to a gunfight.
什么枪
What guns?
这招还挺精明的
Oh, that was actually pretty clever.
杀了他们
Kill them.
"费利西蒂  磁铁箭头装置不会起作用的"
"Felicity, the magnetic-arrow gag will never work."
是的  它会起作用的  亲爱的
Yes, it will, my love,
因为我可聪明得很
because I am really smart.
而你猜怎样  奥利弗  它起作用了
And guess what, Oliver. It did work.
费利西蒂  亲爱的  你在我耳边絮叨
Felicity, honey, it's a little hard to fight
我都没法专心战斗了
with you doing that in my ear.
我忘了这是一个开放频道
Oh, I totally forgot that this was an open line.
继续干你的活吧  做点聪明的决定
Keep doing what you're doing. Make smart decisions.
你知道吗  我必须承认
Ooh! You know, I got to be honest.
我还以为咱们会周旋得更久一些呢
I really thought we'd be doing this dance a lot longer.
晚安啦
Night-night.
那是什么
What was that?
该死
Damn it.
每次都这样
Every time.
是闪电侠
It's The Flash.
我们认识闪电侠吗
Did I know we knew The Flash?
我们认识闪电侠  好的
We know The Flash. Okay.
-我不知道我们认识闪电侠  -谢谢你
- I didn't know we knew The Flash. - Thank you.
但我不觉得你跑这么远是来保护我们的
But I don't think you ran all the way here to protect us.
不  不是来保护你的
No, not to protect you.
我要保护一个朋友
I need to protect a friend.
新家不错啊
Nice new digs.
而且我刚注意到  战袍没有袖子
Also, I just noticed, no sleeves.
你不怕得感冒吗
Don't you get cold?
我耗费了五年的时间生活在
I spent the better part of five years on an island
中国北海的一座小岛上
in the North China Sea.
我不会感冒的  巴里
I don't get cold, Barry.
巴里  看到你太好了
Barry, it's so good to see you.
费利西蒂
Felicity.
很高兴见到你  费利西蒂
Good to see you, Felicity.
你怎么不告诉我极速断了你的背
How come you didn't tell me Zoom broke your back?
-我  -真高兴你没事
- I... - Oh, I'm so glad you're okay.
所以和她约会就是这感觉吗
So this is what it's like dating her?
她给我的瘀伤比丧钟给的还多
More bruises from her than from Deathstroke.
好吧  尖端科研实验室很惊人  但这里
Okay, S.T.A.R. Labs is impressive, but this is...
这里完全搞错了
This is completely wrong!
你们有没有看我送过来的规格书啊
Did you guys even look at the specs I sent over?
这简直是乱七八糟
This is a tragedy.
我为工程学的丧失感到悲哀
I'm mourning for the death of engineering.
用铜线来负责传输来自
Copper wiring to handle the processing speed
帕尔默卫星的数据
from the Palmer Satellite,
不然你的系统会超载的
or else your system is gonna overload.
没有发生这种情况
Yeah, but that hasn't happened.
自从上周以来没有过
I mean, it hasn't happened since last week.
没有...昨天发生过了
I mean, it didn't-It happened yesterday.
我是费利西蒂
I'm Felicity.
我是肯德拉·桑德斯  我是西斯科的...
I'm Kendra Saunders. I'm Cisco's...
她  是我的  漂亮新朋友
She's, uh, my, uh, new, beautiful friend
偶尔会和我接接吻
who kisses me occasionally.
好吧  我是西娅
Right. Um, I'm Thea.
这是约翰·狄格尔  还有我哥哥
This is John Diggle and my brother.
奥利弗·奎恩
Oliver Queen.
好吧  首先我认识了闪电侠
Wow. Okay, first to meet The Flash
现在又认识了绿箭侠
and now the Green Arrow.
你们还有其他惊喜要给我吗
Do you have any other surprises for me?
不要再有惊喜了
Please, no more surprises.
巴里说你需要我们的帮助
Barry said that you need our help.
有个非常危险的人盯上了你
Somebody very dangerous is after you.
是的  而且我完全不知道为什么
Yeah, and I have no idea why.
那家伙究竟长什么样
What does this guy even look like?
等下
Hold on.
好了  这就是他
Okay, this is him.
这种绝活我绝对想不出来
Yeah, see, that's something I would never think of.
这多斯拉克人的样子挺性感
Hey, kind of rocking that Dothraki look--hot.
来让面部识别看看能不能找到匹配
Let's see if facial recognition can find a match.
-就是他  -是啊  奇怪
- That's him. - Yeah, strange.
这照片是1975年的
This picture's from 1975.
也就是说他现在应该八十岁了
Which would make him about 80 years old right now.
还有什么关于他的信息
Okay, what else can you tell us?
他说我们已经认识很久了
He said we've known each other for ages,
但我之前从没见过他
but I've never met the man before.
这里边肯定有什么联系
There has to be some kind of connection.
我想不出来
Not one I can think of.
我六个月前刚搬到中城
I just moved to Central City six months ago.
你为什么要搬到那里去
Why'd you move there?
我就感觉被那城市吸引了
I just felt drawn to the city, I guess.
肯德拉  这人追杀你肯定是有原因的
Kendra, there is a reason this guy's after you.
想想
Think.
你看  我们只是来这里躲一阵子
Look, man, we just came out here to hide out for a bit
直到想出解决办法  你可以放松一点
until we figure things out, so you can just take it down...
你来到这里是因为需要我们的帮助
You came here because you need our help.
我的帮助就是这个样子的
This is what my help looks like.
奥利弗  我刚把你们
Oliver, I just saved you guys
从那群不知道干什么的家伙手中救出来
from whatever the hell Flock of Seagulls was about to do.
你最起码能...
The least you can do is--
巴里  我们都没有超能力
Barry, none of us have superpowers.
你把肯德拉带入我们的世界
You brought Kendra into our world
却不知道她是谁
without knowing who she is
或是这家伙找她到底想要什么
or what this dude that is after her is looking for.
你让我们都陷入了危险
You made all of us unsafe.
要不由你来问问题吧
So maybe you ask the questions.
我们都是朋友  对吧
We're all friends here, right?
要不大伙去我们家
Why don't we go back to our place
喝几杯  然后再聊一聊
and have some drinks, and we can talk?
好
Cool.
你在忙什么
What you working on?
这是一种
This is a formula
能提高极速者速度的配方
meant to increase a speedster's velocity
自从极速出现在我的地球上后我就开始研发了
that I've been developing since Zoom showed up on my earth.
讽刺的是  这本是用来帮助杰伊·加里克的
Ironically, this was meant to help out Jay Garrick.
你想让巴里通过服药而跑得更快吗
You want to give Barry a drug to make him run faster?
是的  短期内增强他体内的神速力
Temporarily enhance the Speed Force in his system, yes.
这么说你是在制造极速者用的加速氮气了
So you're trying to make nitrous oxide for speedsters.
类比得很好  是的  我试过了
Good analogy. Yes, I tried.
我试了五次  失败了五次
Five times I tried. Five times I failed.
这是因为我的专业是技术
That's what you get when your background is technology
而不是生物化学
and not biochemistry.
那你很幸运有我在这
Well, then you are lucky I am here.
什么意思
What does that mean?
你一直是从机械的方面
You've been thinking of this
来考虑这个问题  而不是从生物化学的角度
as a mechanical problem, not a biomechanical one.
这又是什么意思
And what does that mean?
当极速者在奔跑时  会消耗大量的氧气
When a speedster runs, they consume an extraordinary amount of oxygen,
硝酸盐
所以我们只需要一种东西
so we just need something
能在他们奔跑时供给他们多余的氧气就行了
to give an extra boost of oxygen during that time.
例如制氧机
Like an oxygen generator.
没错
Exactly.
所以我们只需要一种
So we just need a chemical
富含氧气的化学物质
that's rich in oxygen that would release it
而且在分解时几乎只释放出氧气
as a nearly pure gas as it decomposes--
比如像是
something like...
-氯酸钠  -氯酸钠
- Sodium chlorate. - Sodium chlorate.
然后我们只需要把它加热就能释放出氧气了
Then all we'd need is heat to release the oxygen.
也就是说用极速者奔跑时产生的闪电就行
Which a speedster generates naturally in the form of lightning.
我觉得这想法能有用
I think something like this just might work.
你觉得你能帮我实现吗
You think you can help me figure it out?
不妨一试
I can certainly try.
我才不要改绰号呢
I'm not changing my nickname.
我喜欢快手这个名字
I like Speedy.
你知道我擅长什么吗
Are you familiar with my body of work?
如果是的话  你就应该知道我能想出
If you are, then you know I can come up with something
比快手更好的名字
so much better than Speedy.
你怎么不去理个发呢
Why don't you get a haircut?
之后我们或许还能谈谈
And then maybe we can talk about it.
我觉得你之所以生气是因为我的护发素太好了
I think you're just mad because my conditioner game is on point.
帕尔默科技的总裁
So the CEO of Palmer Technologies
现在跟奥利弗·奎恩在一起
is living with Oliver Queen.
半年里的变化也太大了吧
It's insane how much life can change in six months?
你肯定比别人更能理解
Which you would know better than anyone,
毕竟又出现了另一个闪电侠
considering that there's another Flash,
另一个威尔斯博士  都是从另一个地球来的
another Dr. Wells, from another... earth.
我是说
I mean...
是的  最近挺乱的
Yeah. No, it's been trippy lately.
我很好奇奥利弗的二重身会是什么样
I wonder what Oliver's doppelganger would look like.
光头  大肚子
Bald, pot-bellied...
和蔼可亲
agreeable.
有女朋友了吗
You seeing anyone?
-有了  其实  -真好
- I am, actually. - Good.
她的名字叫帕蒂
Patty is her name.
她很好
She's amazing.
这才配得上你
You deserve someone amazing.
谢谢
Thanks.
我的肉肠卷好了
My pigs in a blanket!
奥利
Hey, Ollie...
很抱歉你给你带来这么多麻烦
look, I'm sorry that I laid all of this on you.
-我知道这很不公平  -没关系的
- I know that it wasn't fair. - It's okay.
很抱歉我之前有些...
I'm sorry if earlier I was a little...
暴躁
Snippy?
别人还说过更难听的
I have been called worse.
但是我很高兴你能来
No, but I'm glad that you're here.
很高兴你能来找我帮忙
I'm glad you reached out.
这说明你很成熟  我之所以知道
It shows a real maturity, and I would know that
是因为我从没这么成熟过
because I've never been that mature.
我会永远帮助你
I'm always here for you.
谢谢
Thank you.
不得不说  这不像以前那个
I got to say, this isn't the same
我所见到的绿箭团队了
Arrow team I'm used to seeing
你也不是以前的奥利弗·奎恩了
or the same Oliver Queen.
-你好像很  -幸福
- You seem really... - Happy?
-是的  幸福  -我确实很幸福
- Happy, yeah. - I am happy.
我终于得到了我所想要的一切
I finally have everything that I've ever wanted.
跟费利西蒂在一起让我感受到了真正的平和
Being with Felicity has given me a real sense of peace,
这是长久以来我所一直没有的
something that I haven't had in a long time.
你之前不是跟我说我们这种人泡不到妞吗
Didn't you tell me that guys like us don't get the girl?
是的
Yep.
我以前错了
I was wrong.
我提议大家举杯
I would like to propose a toast.
我希望不是因为黑暗时期才让我们聚在一起
I wish it wasn't just the dark times bringing us together.
可因为有了像你这样的朋友
But it is friends like you
就算是黑暗时期也值了
that make those dark times worth having.
这人啊
What a guy.
抢了我酒  还抢了我的台词
Steals my drinks, steals my words.
就像我之前说的  很高兴见到大家
As I was saying, it's good to see everyone.
-没错  -干杯
- Yes. - Cheers.
干杯
Cheers.
-干杯  -干杯
- Cheers. - Cheers.
别担心了  好吧
Look, don't worry, all right?
我们会保护她的安全
We're gonna keep her safe.
-我保证  -我知道
- I promise. - Yeah, I know.
有件事我没告诉过你
Look, there's something I never told you.
第一次亲肯德拉时  我有了震波反应
The first time I kissed Kendra, I got a vibe.
不是那种反应
No, not like that kind of vibe.
是用震波感应到了她
Like, I vibed vibed.
记得有翅膀的男人吗
Remember the man with wings?
那不是什么男人
It wasn't a man.
那是肯德拉
It was Kendra.
她就像是只大鸟
She was, like, a bird.
你觉得她是超能力者
You think that she's a meta-human?
等等  你怎么不早点说出来
Wait. Why didn't you say anything about this sooner?
我当时没想到这事有什么关系
Well, I didn't think it was related,
但是看来的确是有
but I guess now it has to be.
我不想她知道我的超能力
Look, I don't want her to know about my powers.
我和她之间相处得非常好
I have this great thing going with her.
她喜欢我的笑话  爱看电影
She laughs at my jokes, and she loves movies, and...
我只是  以前从没有过这种感觉
I just-- I've never felt like this before,
我不想破坏它
and I don't want to sabotage it.
我明白这种感觉
I get the feeling.
快看
Look!
我总是会找到你的  茶雅拉
I will always find you, Chay-Ara.
-别动  -那我要怎么杀死你们
- Don't move. - Then how will I kill you all?
我也可以做到
Yeah, I can do that too.
西娅  别
Thea, no!
你干了什么
What did you do?
我收了尾
I ended it.
这就我们要提问的原因
This is why we ask questions.
等等  他去哪了
Wait. W-where did he go?
天呐
Oh, boy.
好吧
Okay.
谢谢
Thanks.
好了  一有消息  兰斯会打电话来
All right, Lance is gonna call if he gets any information on...
不管这人是谁
whoever that is.
我知道上哪能找到些资料
I know where we can get some info.
肯德拉  我有超能力
Kendra, I have powers.
我能用震波感应人
I get these vibes from people.
都是超能力者的影像
They're visions of meta-humans,
我看到了你的
and I had one of you.
第一  你是说你是超能力者
So, A, you're saying you're a meta-human,
第二  她也是超能力者
and, B, she's a meta-human?
我不知道
I don't know.
在这些影像中  你能飞
In these visions, you could fly.
就像你是一只鸟之类的东西
It was like you were a bird of some sort.
-一只鸟  -是的
- A bird? - Yeah.
你还看到了什么
What else did you see?
只有这些  只有带着翅膀的你
That's it-- just you with wings.
我怎么没想到这点
Oh, I did not see that one coming.
我想有很多事你们都没想到
Oh, I think there's a lot you didn't see coming.
好极了  更多的惊喜  他是谁
Great. More surprises. Who the hell is this?
是我爸爸
It's my dad.
我想我成功了
I think I did it.
想不到啊  斯诺
What do you know, Snow?
你的确成功了
I think you did do it.
终极速度-6
Velocity-6?
这就是非常紧急的事吗  哈里森
This is what was so urgent, Harrison?
你叫我来就是为了试试你的神速药吗
You get me to come here so I can take your speed drug?
没错
That's right.
-你知道这件事  -她当然知道
- You knew about this. - Of course she did.
是她想出来的
She figured it out.
我以为这是为了帮助巴里
I thought this was to help Barry.
的确是为了帮助巴里
It is to help Barry,
所以我们要在体内存有神速力的人
which is why we need to do test runs on subjects
身上做一些测试
who once had the Speed Force in their system.
神速力不是这样用的
The Speed Force doesn't work like that.
那不是在实验室里能创造出来的
It's not something you can create in a lab.
你以为你怎么成为闪电侠的  加里克
How do you think you became The Flash, Garrick?
就是因为我和实验室
By me and a lab.
科学让你  巴里和极速拥有了超能力
Science is what did this to you, to Barry, to Zoom,
而科学正是我们阻止极速的方法
and science is what we need to stop Zoom,
也是唯一的方法
and this is our only option.
再找别的方法
Find another one.
神速力无法复制  也无法增强
The Speed Force can't be replicated or enhanced.
它不是死物
It's a living thing.
而是赐予我的礼物
It's a gift that was given to me.
这药  你完全不知道它会有什么反应
That drug-- you have no idea what it's gonna do.
我不会再让你们在我身上
I'm not going to let another one of your experiments
做实验瞎搞  哈里森
mess with me again, Harrison.
去找别人做你的小白鼠吧
You find someone else to be your guinea pig.
杰伊
Jay.
凯特琳  血清要离巴里远点
Caitlin, keep that serum away from Barry.
你要去哪
Where are you going?
去拿我们需要的东西
To pick up what we need.
等等  杰伊刚说我们不该把它交给巴里
Wait. Jay just said we shouldn't give it to Barry.
我们要做该做的事
We're gonna do what we need.
你要找的人是汪达尔·萨维奇
The man you're looking for is Vandal Savage.
汪达尔·萨维奇  没听说过
Vandal Savage? Never heard of him.
他是谁
Well, who is he?
有人说他是成吉思汗最信任的导师
Some say he was the most trusted adviser to Genghis Khan.
有人说他指导凯撒大帝如何打败高卢战争
Others say he guided Julius Caesar through the Gallic Wars.
但是刺客联盟能确定的一件事就是
But one thing the League knows for sure--
这些事他都参与过
he was there for all of it.
那你意思是
So what are you saying?
他是吸血鬼什么的吗
He's like a vampire or something?
不是吸血鬼  而是不死之身
Not a vampire, an Immortal.
我们已经正式进入疯狂中
Okay, we've officially stepped into crazy town.
不死之身
Immortality?
等等  不不不  这说得通
Wait. No, no, no, this makes sense.
这解释了为何他的样子跟1975年时的一样
This explains why he looks the same as he did in 1975.
这不可能
This can't be possible.
目前你没有任何办法可以救她
There's nothing you can do to save her now.
肯德拉  别听他的
Kendra, do not listen to him.
我要去透透气
I-I just need some air.
我们会全力保护肯德拉
We're gonna do whatever we have to to keep Kendra safe,
不管你认为我们是否能做到
whether you think we can or not.
乔  我是帕蒂
Hey, Joe, it's Patty.
我刚才向一位武器专家
I just interviewed a weapons
咨询了那个袭击者所用的燧石刀
expert about the flint knife our attacker used.
然后发现了很有意思的事
Found out something pretty interesting,
打给我
uh, so call me back.
哈里森·威尔斯
Harrison Wells?
肯德拉
Kendra!
你没事儿吧
You going to be all right?
只是一时间信息量有点大
It's just a lot to take in right now.
我很抱歉没有跟你说明我的情况
Look, I'm sorry I didn't tell you about me before.
我不想让你我之间的关系变质
I didn't want things to be different between us.
跟这无关  西斯科
It's not that, Cisco.
如果大家所说的都是真的
If what everyone's saying is true--
并且现在看来很有可能就是这样
and it's beginning to seem like it is--
我整个人生就不一样了
my whole life just changed,
但我却还没有准备好
and I am so not ready for that.
我明白你的意思  真的
I hear what you're saying. I do.
我刚发现我有超能力的时候
When I first learned about my powers,
也是这种感觉
I remember feeling that exact same feeling,
现在我还会有那种感觉
and sometimes I still feel that way,
我想说的是...
and all I can say is...
每过一天都会离正常的生活更近一步
every day gets a little bit more normal.
我向你保证
I promise you.
谢谢你
Thank you.
别这么客气
You're so welcome.
肯德拉
Kendra!
救命
Help!
有什么发现吗
Guys, did you find anything?
正在找
I'm on it!
这可是我的地盘
This is my house.
别担心  我们会找到她的
Don't worry. We're going to find her.
你依旧这么美
You look as beautiful as ever.
茶雅拉  是我啊  胡夫
Chay-Ara, it's me, Khufu.
还记得吗
Do you remember?
看着我
Look at me.
你需要清醒过来
You need to wake up.
你在说什么
What are you talking about?
我不知道你是谁
I don't know who you are.
你展现真我时就会知道了
You will once you emerge.
在那之前  你要待在我身边
Until then, you need to stay by my side
这样我就可以保护你
so that I can protect you.
保护我不受谁的伤害
Protect me? From what?
追捕你的人  汪达尔·萨维奇
The man who's hunting you, Vandal Savage.
第57大街塔楼
找到他们了  第57大街塔楼上
I got them! 57th Street tower.
我就在那附近
I'm right near there.
看你工作真是件让人愉悦的事  斯莫克
Always a pleasure watching you work, Smoak.
我并没有使劲
That was pitiful.
我明白你难以理解
I know this is a lot to take in,
但在这件事上你一定要相信我  我...
but you sort of just kind of have to trust me on this. I...
等我一下  待在这别动
Just one second. Stay right there.
我看到他了
I got eyes on him.
把那女孩交出来
Give me the girl.
想都别想  罗宾汉
Not gonna do that, Robinhood.
你犯了个很严重的错误
You're making a big mistake.
我愿意冒险尝试
I'll take my chances.
巴里  地点变了
Barry, change of venue.
鸟人和奥利弗在第54大街和汽车交口  快去
Birdman and Oliver are at 54th and Motor now--hurry!
马上到
On my way!
我们得让他把翅膀暴露出来
We need to expose his wings.
我接受建议
I'm open to suggestions.
这会儿你听我的了
Now you're listening to me?
这是你的主场  奥利弗
It's your city, Oliver.
好吧
All right.
新技能啊
That's new.
是啊  还算好用
Yep, comes in handy.
我们不能在巴里身上使用这个血清
We can't use that serum on Barry.
这得由他决定  对吧
That's up to him, isn't it?
如果巴里想要阻止极速  这正是他需要的
If Barry wants to stop Zoom, this is what he needs.
杰伊曾说过它有可能伤到巴里
Jay said it could hurt Barry.
杰伊是个懦夫
Well, Jay's a coward.
杰伊是位很了解高速者的科学家
Jay's a scientist who knows a lot about speedsters.
你也是个科学家  斯诺  你监测过巴里
You're a scientist, Snow. You've been watching Barry.
你明白他现在的速度远远不够用
You know he's nowhere near as fast as he needs to be.
他的另一位导师  另一个哈里森·威尔斯
This other mentor, this other Harrison Wells,
不想让他将潜能完全发掘出来  但我想
did not want him to reach his full potential--I do.
你的口气现在跟他越来越像了
You know, you're really starting to sound a lot like him.
举起手来
Put your hands in the air.
-你是谁  -你被捕了
- Who are you? - You're under arrest.
麦吉博士说得没错
Doctor McGee was right.
-她看到的确实是你  -克里斯蒂娜·麦吉
- She did see you. - Christina McGee?
水星实验室的
At Mercury Labs.
你是哈里森·威尔斯
You're Harrison Wells.
没错  我是哈里森·威尔斯
Yes, I'm Harrison Wells.
我不是那个哈里森
I'm not the Harrison--
站住  再靠近我就开枪了
Stop! You move closer, and I'll shoot.
把枪交给我...
Give me that--
天啊  你做了什么
Oh, my God, what have you done?
哈里森
Harrison?
哈里森  坚持住
Harrison, stay with me.
哈里森  哈里森  坚持住
Harrison, Harrison, stay with me.
坚持住  哈里森  拜托
Stay with me, Harrison, come on.
你为什么向他开枪
Why did you shoot him?
我以为那是把枪  对不起  我打911
I thought that was a gun. I'm sorry. I'll call 911.
不  不要打
No, don't!
-为什么  -因为这
- Why? - Because this--
乔·韦斯特没给你解释这一切吗
Didn't Joe West explain this to you?
-没有  -给乔打电话
- No. - Just call Joe.
好
Okay.
她在哪儿
Where is she?
你叫什么名字
What's your name?
你们这是在置她于危险之中
You're putting her in danger,
我是唯一有能力拯救她的人
and I'm the only one capable of saving her.
你在"拯救"一词的理解上
You have a very interesting perspective
有非常独特的见解啊
on what the word "saving" means.
她是我的毕生挚爱  小姑娘
She's the love of my lifetime, sweetheart.
我不会伤害她的
I was not gonna hurt her.
你们得放我走
You need to let me go.
茶雅拉
Chay-Ara.
我的名字是肯德拉·桑德斯
My name is Kendra Saunders.
在这一世而已
In this life.
而我是  曾经是卡特·哈尔
And I am--was Carter Hall,
但这都不是我们的真实身份
but that is not who we are.
什么意思
What does that mean?
你是女祭司茶雅拉  我是王子胡夫
You're Priestess Chay-Ara. I'm Prince Khufu.
我们是恋人
And we're lovers.
灵魂伴侣
Soul mates.
四千年来我们一直在一起
We've been partners for 4,000 years.
每一次轮回我们都彼此吸引  我们死后
We're drawn to each other in each life, and after we die,
又转世轮回寻找对方  一世又一世
we reincarnate to find each other again and again and again.
现在我已经找到你了
And now that I've found you,
我们得离开这里了
we should really get out of here.
够了  罗密欧  就不可以消停一下吗
Okay, Romeo, why don't you pump the brakes?
这些人无法再保护你不受萨维奇伤害了
These people cannot protect you from Savage any longer.
你知道汪达尔·萨维奇是谁吗
Do you know who Vandal Savage is?
每一次转世  他都会狩猎并杀死我们
In every lifetime, he hunts us down and kills us.
他过去成功了两百零六次
He's done it 206 times,
我不准备让他成功两百零七次
and I'm not planning to make it 207.
他为什么要杀你们
Why does he kill you?
他的生命力与我们的紧密相连
His life force is tethered to ours.
每杀死我们一次  他就会变得更加强大
Every time he kills us, he becomes more powerful.
你们可以自己算算
You do the math.
两百零六次你都输了
You're 0 for 206,
你还认为自己是保护她的最佳人选
and you still think you're her best bet, hmm?
好  那我们要做的就是找到萨维奇
Okay, so what we need to do is just find Savage
并解决掉他
and get rid of him.
我的朋友  你没法解决掉他
Well, you can't get rid of him, my friend.
是吗  那就睁大眼瞧清楚了
Oh, yeah? Watch us.
可能比你们想像的要难
It might be harder than you think.
这家伙就只知道这种出场方式吗
Is that the only way this guy knows how to enter a room?
我的同伴告诉我
My associates tell me
萨维奇几小时前离开了星城
Savage left Star City a few hours ago.
-去哪儿了  -我们也不确定
- For where? - We're not quite sure.
但我猜想在他和你们交手后
But I assume after his run-in with you,
他意识到需要更强大的武器
he realized he needed something more powerful
来完成自己的目标
to complete his mission.
我们认为他在找荷鲁斯权杖
We think he's trying to locate the Staff of Horus.
不好意思  那是个啥
Sorry, what is that?
是我们过去的一件古物
It's a relic from our past--
一件古老而强大的武器
an ancient and powerful weapon.
要是萨维奇得到了它
If Savage gets his hands on it,
那要阻止他几乎是不可能的了
it's going to be nearly impossible to stop him.
我们的生活
Since when did our lives
何时突然变成《夺宝奇兵》了
suddenly become an "Indiana Jones" movie?
-费利西蒂  -在
- Felicity? - Yeah?
你能找到它吗
Think you can find it?
能  可能在某个博物馆里吧
Yeah. It's probably at some museum somewhere.
开动我的魔法  看看我能发现点什么
I'll, uh, work my magic, see what I can find.
我们没时间了
We're running out of time.
你现在需要展现真我
You need to emerge now.
拜托  你要怎么才肯相信我
Come on, what is it gonna take for you to believe me?
你也看见我的翅膀了啊
You saw my wings.
我明白你知道这是真的
I know you know this is true.
求你让我教你吧
Please, just let me show you how.
-他怎么样了  -他现在缺氧
- How's he doing? - He's losing oxygen.
-你给我离开这里  -乔  我
- I need you to leave. - Joe, I--
帕蒂  走
Patty, go.
子弹打在了他肺动脉的某个分支上
There's a bullet in a branch of his pulmonary artery
堵住了左肺大部分的血液流动
that's blocking off most of the blood flow from the left lung.
你可以把那子弹取出来吗
Are we able to get the bullet out?
那样会造成更大的伤害
Not without causing too much damage.
我需要杰伊帮忙
I need Jay's help.
那么
So...
你想让我跳下去
you just want me to jump.
跌落  跳  燕式跳水  随你喜欢
Fall, jump, swan dive, whatever suits you.
只要跳了就对了
Just, uh, do it.
够了  这不是《世界极限运动会》
Okay, this isn't the X Games.
所以这就是她展现真我的方式
And this is how she emerges--
跳下去  直面死亡才能直面真我
she just falls towards her death?
没错  四千年的经历证明就是如此
Yep. 4,000 years of experience says that's exactly how.
睁大眼睛看着吧
Just watch and learn.
不行  不好意思  我们这是在干啥啊
No, I'm sorry. What are we doing?
我们为什么要听他的啊
Why are we listening to this guy?
奥利弗
Come on, Oliver,
你才是那个该问问题的人
you're supposed to be the one who asks questions.
好  但在经历了我们所见和西斯科所说的后
Okay, but after what we saw, after what Cisco said,
真不敢相信我会这么说  但是
I cannot believe I'm going to say this, but it...
貌似还挺有道理的
kind of makes sense.
我得试试
I need to try.
你说真的吗
Are you serious?
没错
Yes, she is.
巴里
Barry!
你为什么要那么做
What the hell was that?
为了救她的命
Saving her life.
你应该开始展现真我的
You should have emerged.
你被什么妨碍着
Something is blocking you.
也许我们应该再试一次  看看...
Well, we should just try again and see what's...
-不  -不  不  不
- No! - Yeah, no, no, no, no.
我们不会再那么做了
We're not doing that again.
肯德拉  你不需要这么做
Kendra, you don't have to do this.
奥利弗  我们能阻止萨维奇  好吗
Oliver, we can stop Savage, okay?
巴里  巴里
Barry. Barry!
什么
What?
能和你谈一下吗
Talk to you for a second?
好吧
Okay.
看着他点
Keep an eye on him.
你怎么回事
What is going on with you?
我在试着救她的命
I'm trying to keep her alive.
我们应该让她跳
Then I think we let her jump.
你在开玩笑吗
Are you kidding?
巴里  我理解你非常想帮忙
Barry, I get that you're desperate to help
你想做个英雄
and you want to be the hero
你想靠自己救她的命
and you want to save her yourself,
但是我觉得她有自己决定的权利
but I think she has to have a part in it too.
什么
What?
只是现在这些规则不停变化
It's just--the rules keep changing.
之前我必须要穿越时间
One day I have to run through time,
后来我还需要和心电感应的大猩猩作战
the next I'm fighting a telepathic gorilla,
而现在呢
and now we're what?
我们要找一个在狂暴追杀
We're chasing down an immortal madman on a rampage
转世女战神的永生疯子
against down a reincarnated warrior priestess?
我只是从没想过当我拥有了超能力之后
I just never thought I'd have superpowers
竟然比之前没超能力时还无助
and feel more powerless than I ever have in my entire life.
这个我能理解
That part I understand.
但是你已经帮助肯德拉了
But you have already helped Kendra.
你保住了她的命
You have kept her alive.
所以现在帮她找回她的翅膀
So now let's help her get her wings,
这样她就可以带你飞回中城
and then she can give you a lift back to Central City.
中城
Central City.
-怎么了  -你应该去中城寻找权杖
- What? - You need to check Central City for the staff.
肯德拉  你之前说你是被吸引过去的
Kendra, you said you were drawn there.
-是的  -我想你是被能摧毁你的东西吸引
- Yeah. - I think you're drawn to things that destroy you
就像你们两个之间的吸引力一样
the same way you two are drawn to each other.
博物馆和私人收藏都找不到
That's why it wasn't in any museum or private collection,
是因为八个月前被中城的
because it was consecrated eight months ago
圣马克教堂供起来了
at St. Mark's in Central City.
我们必须赶在萨维奇之前拿到它
We've got to get it before Savage does.
卡特  待在这
Carter, stay here.
我哪都不会去
I'm not going anywhere.
打电话给西娅和狄格尔
Call Thea and Digg,
我们需要他们过来守着
and we'll have them hold down the fort
以防萨维奇出现
in case Savage shows up.
肯德拉  去年我也失去了我的能力
Kendra, last year, I lost my powers.
我把它找回来的唯一方式就是
The only way I could get them back
我把身边发生的一切事情都抛开
is if I just forgot about everything happening around me
只关注在我自己身上
and focused on who I was.
相信自己  你就能展现真我
Just believe in yourself, and your true self will emerge.
谢谢
Thanks.
你确定你要这么做吗
Hey, are you sure that you want to do this?
如果这是个永生的人
If this guy's immortal
权杖真的像梅林说的那么厉害
and Merlyn's right about how powerful this staff is...
我们会没事的
We'll be fine.
吻她
Kiss her.
我们会没事的
We'll be fine.
-当心点  -我们走
- Careful. - Let's go.
什么情况
Now what?
他的心缩压在下降
His systolic pressure's dropping.
他的心脏会停止
He's gonna code.
有多糟
How bad is it?
在他的肺动脉里有颗子弹
There's a bullet in his pulmonary artery.
我把它取出来  你能缝合伤口吗
Can you close the wound if I get it?
能
Yes.
你要怎么做
How are you going to do that?
那是什么
What is that?
这是一种叫做终极速度-6的血清
It's a serum called Velocity-6.
能够让杰伊暂时拥有神速力
It could give Jay temporary speed.
他能够穿透威尔斯博士的胸口
He can phase through Doctor Wells' chest
取出子弹
and remove the bullet.
是的  但是我和你说过
Yeah, but I told you,
我不知道我使用了那个之后会有什么后果
I have no idea what's gonna happen if I use that.
这是我们唯一的选择
It's our only option.
如果你不这么做  威尔斯博士会死
If you don't do this, Dr. Wells will die.
启动了
It's working.
血压和含氧量在上升
BP and oxygenation is rising.
血液开始向他的肺部回流
Blood flow's returning to his lungs.
谢谢你
Thank you.
我在想
I was just thinking...
以前我感觉与众不同的时候
all the moments of my life when I felt different,
就好像我出了什么问题
like something was wrong with me.
现在我知道原因了
Now I know why.
一切都会好的
It's gonna be all right.
好吗
Okay?
我知道人生突然有重大改变
Look, I-I know what it's like to have your life
是怎样的心情
suddenly change like this.
我可以帮你熬过去的
I-I can help you get through this.
我不知道你做不做得到
I don't know if you can.
西斯科  现在我有了完全不一样的生活
Cisco, there's a whole other life inside me,
我需要好好了解这其中包含了什么
hundreds of lives, that I need to know about.
我需要自己去了解
I think I need to do it by myself.
我要...
I have to...
追寻我的命运
embrace my destiny.
我要相信
I have to believe.
你不用那么做
You don't have to do this.
怎么了
What's going on?
没什么  我只是想如常快速进入室内
Nothing. I just like to speed into rooms, usually.
我们能在哪里找到它
Where do you think we find this thing?
我有段时间没来教堂了
I haven't been in one of these places in a while.
我们来得太晚了
We're too late.
你一般不说这句话的吧
Something you're not used to saying very often,
我想
I'd imagine.
你试过你的那些箭了  不是吗
You tried those arrows once before, remember?
那时它们无法完成任务  现在能了吗
They didn't quite finish the job, now, did they?
我不会再犯同样的错误
I'm not gonna make that mistake again.
放过肯德拉
You're gonna leave Kendra alone.
我做不到
I can't do that.
我注定要永生
While my destiny is to live forever,
茶雅拉注定要死  你们也是
Chay-Ara's is to die, as is yours now.
-我们该怎么做  -你现在愿意听我的了吗
- Any ideas? - Oh, now you'll listen to me?
这是你的城市
It's your city.
好吧  把权杖抢过来
All right, let's just try to get the staff.
好吧  跟我的指示
All right, on my mark.
好吧
All right.
卡特说得对
Carter was right.
我被妨碍着
Something's holding me back.
也许是中城  或者是你
Maybe it's Central City or you
或者是我对我人生的想法
or what I thought my life was gonna be,
但如果我不放手  我就无法成为真正的自己
but I'm never gonna become who I really am unless I let go.
我必须这么做
I have to do this.
[古语]
在我过去的岁月里
In all my countless years,
我从来没有遇过你们这种强敌
I've never encountered anybody with your capabilities.
惊叹
Astonishing!
不
No!
茶雅拉
Chay-Ara.
天呐
Oh, my God!
我一向喜欢慢速死亡
I used to enjoy slow deaths.
现在我觉得那样很无聊了
Now I just find them boring.
谢谢
Thanks.
他会不会把自己炸死了
Any chance he blew himself up in there?
不太可能
Not likely.
所以打平手了吧
So that's, like, a tie, right?
-应该吧  -我认为是
- I guess. - I will take it.
你没事吧
You okay?
我要学会怎么样用这些玩意儿
I'm gonna have to learn how to use these things.
你很快就会学会了  鹰女
You'll get the hang of it, Hawkgirl.
威尔斯博士
Dr. Wells?
你会没事的
You're gonna be okay.
这是个好消息
That's good news.
不过你可能要疼上好一阵了
You will probably be very sore for a little while, though.
疼痛总比死亡好
Sore is better than dead.
没错
Yes, it is.
你怎么样了  加里克
How are you doing, Garrick?
你的血清已经从我体内排出
Your serum's out of my system,
我不会再拿来用了
and I will never take it again.
杰伊
Jay...
谢谢
thank you.
你别让巴里使用终极速度-6就是答谢我了
You can thank me by keeping that Velocity-6 away from Barry.
是奥利弗
That was Oliver.
萨维奇取走了荷鲁斯权杖
Savage has the Staff of Horus.
他要我们所有人尽快赶往中城
He wants us all in Central City as soon as possible.
好  劳蕾尔在那里探望她母亲
Okay, well, Laurel's already there visiting her mom,
我会打去通知她我们正在赶过去
so I'll call her and let her know we're coming by.
萨维奇去了中城
If Savage is in Central City,
我们为什么还要去那里
then why are we going back there?
去结束这一切
So we can end this.
只有巴里和奥利弗
And if anybody's gonna take down Savage,
可以打败萨维奇
it's going to be Barry and Oliver.
而且你展现真我了
Plus, you've emerged.
他的胜算变低了
It's going to be much harder for him now.
大家齐心协力
And together, all of us,
就能一次解决他
we can take him down once and for all.
我们要怎么过去
Okay, so how are we gonna get there?
我告诉过你我是
Did I mention I'm the CEO
一家拥有私人飞机的大公司的总裁吗
of a big company with a private jet?
闪电侠特饮
这是什么时候的事
Since when is that a thing?
多加一份浓缩咖啡的特调咖啡
八个月前
About eight months.
如果你拯救星城  可能也会有
Maybe if you save Star City, you might get one too.
还有  我们要抓住萨维奇
By the way, we still need to get Savage.
我们会抓住他的
We'll get him.
小心点  小兄弟
Watch yourself, buddy.
你不想丢了你的英雄
You don't want to lose this guy.
-谢谢你  先生  -不用客气
- Thanks, mister. - Yeah.